Guide to the May Anti-Slavery manuscript collection, 1749-1933.
May Anti-Slavery manuscript collection
- Series IV. Correspondence and Documents from Other Abolitionists
  - A-F
    - Ball, Mason C., December 20, 1869 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      Letter of recommendation written by Wake, Ransom F.; 5 paychecks
    - Wm. Ballantyne, November 30, 1869; Ballantyne, William (Box 9, Folder 47)
      Itemized Receipt for York, Charlotte L.
    - Ballou, Adin, 1845-1846 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Barbour, Alfred M., December 8, 1859 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Bardwell, F.W., April 22, 1865 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      List of deaths incident to 3d U.S.C.T.; unknown
    - Barker, Edward, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Barker, Matilda, 1869 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      3 paychecks
    - Barnard, Eusebius, April 10, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Barnard, Simon, November 9, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Barnes, E.A., July 29, 1867 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      Application for teaching position; recommendations from Hurlburt, John S. and Miles, D.W.
    - Barnes, J.W.L., November 9, 1859 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      Letter/s to Hoyt, George H.; McKim, James Miller; unknown
    - Barnes, Stuart, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Manly, R.M.
      Buffum, George R.
    - A.S. Barnes & Co., 1868-1869 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      Itemized receipts for Bacon, Harriet E.; Belden, Diana A.; Bent, Catherine R.; Cardoza, T.W.; Goodyear, C.P.; Merrick, Chloe; National Freedmen's Relief; Shaw, Francis George; Smith, J.P.; Stratton, Maggie E.
    - Barnswell, Paul Gustav, 1864-1865 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      Recomendations for a teaching position written by Cain, Richard H.; Fasyth, Jno; and Wilsons, Henery M.
    - Bartlett, Bryant, January 2, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Bates, Martin W., 1847 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      Letter/s to Hunn, John; McKim, James Miller
    - Beach, L.A., February 5, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Beam, Henry D., 1866-1867 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Beaman, Charles W., Jr., 1866-1867 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - Beecher, Charles, July 14, 1853 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Beecher, Henry Ward, October 17, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Orton, May E.
    - Beeman, Eunice M., August 22, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Aldrich, C.S. and Sutphen, G.W.; 3 diplomas; 4 paychecks; 1 newspaper clipping
    - Beers, John C., October 28, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Letter/s to Young, John Russell
    - Belden, Diana A., 1869 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      7 paychecks
    - Bell, Louis A., October 24, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Wilson, William J.
    - Bellows, Henry Whitney, 1865-1870 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Telfer, William Daft
    - Benjamin, Judah Philip, August 4, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Autograph
    - Bennett, Elizabeth P., 1866 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      3 letters of application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Freeman, Sarah P.; 2 paychecks; 2 receipts for salary
    - Bigelow, J., May 26, 1860 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Billingsley, A.S., December 11, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Letter/s to Simpson, Matthew
    - Bingham, John A., July 24, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Bird, F.W., December 11, 1862 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Birge, Mattie, 1868-1869 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Birney, William, 1863-1869 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Weld, Theodore Dwight
    - Bishop, Nathan, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Blair, William, January 14, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Bolles, J.N., November 20, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Bolton, John, July 10, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Bond, Charles W., Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Bond, Edward P., June 30, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Bond, Hugh Lennox, 1866-1869 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Shaw, Francis George; unknown
      Chase, Salmon Portland
    - Bond, S.A., 1869 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      Receipts; 10 paychecks
    - Bonthron, John, December 23, 1818 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Last Will and Testament
    - Boswell, Ignatius, January 8, 1779 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Letter/s to Stone, M.F. (for Grace Stone)
    - Bosworth, Libbi A., November 16, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Miller, L. Merrill and Petiebone, R.G.
    - Botts, Fannie J., September 21, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Dennett, N.C. and Hanson, Dahl D.
    - Bouron, Almira (Allie), 1868-1869 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Walrad, Maggie E.
    - Bowen, G.J., February 18, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Bowen, John W., 1866 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Bowser, James H., February 18, 1869 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Bradburn, George, December 21, 1843 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Bradford, Arthur B., June 25, 1861 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Bradshaw, John, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Branch, Eli G., 1867 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      Letter/s to Holmes, H.B.; McKim, James Miller
    - Brawner, H., Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
      Inventory of the estate of Edelin, Philip
    - Brewer, D.R., December 6, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      Crane, Jane Eliza
    - Brewer, Fisk P., June 9, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      Letter/s to Andrew, C.R.
      Abbott, Lyman
    - Brewster, W.L., December 17, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Brinkerhoff, Isaac W., 1867 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - British and Foreign Anti-Slavery Society, 1840-1841 (Box 10, Folder 44.5-44.6)
      Resolution recording its high estimation of Stanton, Henry Brewster; Stanton, Henry Brewster
    - British & Foreign School Society, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      Invoice for American National Freedmen's Aid Union to Messrs. Johnson & Johnson
    - Brodie, Alice, 1868-1869 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      5 paychecks
    - Brooke, C.A., March 28, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Brooks, Frederick, April 16, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Brooks, Mary L., December 28, 1869 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Brooks, Phillips, 1866-1867 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Brooks, William G., February 12, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Brown, Annie, 1859-1861 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Bell, March 6, 1860 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Brown, Watson
    - Brown, David Paul, 1851 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Pierce, William S.
    - Brown, Henry Box, April 3, 1850 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Brown, James Henry, April 1, 1870 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      1 paycheck
    - Brown, John, 1851-1861 (Box 11, Folder 5.1-5.93)
      Letter/s to Jenkins, Josiah Whipple; McIntosh, Ralph; Song of (old John Brown)
    - Brown, Martha, January 31, 1860 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Mary Ann Day (Mrs. John), 1860-1863 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Letter/s to Bullard, Edward Fitch; McKim, James Miller
    - Brown, Samuel Gilman, July 16, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Brown, Sarah V.V., March 2, 1869 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Watson, 1859 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Letter/s to Brown, Bell
    - Browne, Sara G., 1866 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Monthly report to McKim, James Miller; McKim, James Miller
    - Brownlie, James, September 3, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Buckingham, William Alfred, February 14, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Buckley, C.W., June 11, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Letter/s to Abbott, Lyman
    - Budd, Libbie F., July 27, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Buffum, Arnold, 1832 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Letter/s to Jocelyn, Simeon Smith
    - Buffum, George R., February 14, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Letter/s to Barnes, Stuart
    - Bullard, Julia E., February 17, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Bullock, W.R., September 7, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Burbank, A.C., 1866-1867 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Letter/s to Hawkins, William George; Kennedy, Crammond
    - Burbank, Mr. & Mrs. A.C., August 29, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Hoyt, Joseph and Perry, Allen; 11 expense lists and receipts; 1 paycheck
    - Burghduff, J.W., December 14, 1868 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Letter/s to Collins, Ellen; 1 receipt; 1 paycheck
    - Burleigh, C. M., April 17, 1842 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Burleigh, Charles Calistus, 1839-1844 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
    - Burr, Jona, November 2, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Letter/s to Collyer, Robert; Note to McKim, James Miller from Collyer
    - Burr, Raymond J., 1866-1867 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Letter/s to Hunt, B.P.; McKim, James Miller
    - Burt, D., 1866-1868 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Burt, Mary Elizabeth, December 9, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Burton, N.J., 1867 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Elwell, Rebecca; Rouviere, Fannie
    - Buxton, Sir Thomas Folwell, June 8, 1833 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Cadbury, B.H., 1865-1869 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Cadbury, Joel, 1866-1867 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Cadbury, Richard, 1866-1867 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Callaway, C.R., 1870 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      2 paychecks
    - Calvert, J.W., 1858 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      Letter/s to Hallowell, Joshua L.
    - Cameron, Simon, September 27, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Camp, Fanny V., 1870 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Campbell, Adelaide, August 15, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 39?)
      Letter/s to May, Samuel Joseph
    - Canfield, E.H., 1867 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Canfield, S.A. Martha?, Undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Cannon, John M.*, December 7, 1843 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      Letter/s to
    - Cantwell, I.Y., February 12, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      Letter/s to Stewart, George H.
    - Cardoza, T.W. and L.J., 1870 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Carter, Walter S., March 12, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Cather, A, October 19, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Cecil, R., June 9, 1803 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      Letter/s to Wilberforce, William
    - Chamerovzow, L.A., 1853-1867 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Channing, William Ellery, 1842 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      Letter/s to Child, Lydia Maria; McKim, James Miller; unknown
      Chapman, Maria Weston
    - Chapin, J.H., 1866-1868 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Shaw, Francis George
    - Chapman, Amy L., October 12, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Chase, C. Thurston, 1866-1869 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      McKim, James Miller
    - Chase, Nellie M., August 29, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Bond, E.P. and Pierce, Adelaide P.; 4 paychecks
    - Chase, Pliny Earle, May 16, 1866 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Chase, Salmon Portland, 1865-1868 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      Letter/s to Abbott, Lyman; Bond, Hugh Lennox; McKim, James Miller; Wright, Thomas G.
      Yulee, E
    - No Folder 55, Undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Chase, Supply, 1866-1867 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Chauncey, E., January 31, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Cheney, Ednah Dow, 1866-1867 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Chesson, F.W., September 18, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      Letter/s to Estlin, Mary A.
    - Chew, Joseph, 1870 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Chichester, D.P. and Fanny, December 25, 1831 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      (Deed of gift) to Chichester, Richard; "A list of my lands"
    - Child, David Lee, 1830-1863 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      Portrait; Quotation; Child, Lydia Maria; McKim, James Miller; Sargent, Henrietta
    - Child, Francis James, 1865-1866 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - A Christian friend, August 14, 1860 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Chur, Jacob F., August 23, 1869 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Citizens of Pontiac, IL, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Citizens of San Francisco, July 1867 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Clapp, Mary (Mrs. Dexter E.), 1866 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      2 applications for teaching positions; Recommendation from Horace, James and E. Whittlesey
    - Clark, E.W., 1866-1867 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Letter/s to Garrison, Wendell Phillips; McKim, James Miller
    - Clark, Helen A., October 12, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Clark, John B., 1866-1866 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Clark, M.C., September 10, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Letter/s to Suitterlin, J.E.
    - Clarke, William E., January 15, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Clarkson, Thomas, June 15, 1819 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Clemmer, M.K., July 17, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Application for teaching position; Recommendations from Brackett, N.C.; Johnson, Oliver; Paine, C.G.G.
    - Cleveland, Charles Dexter, August 16, 1858 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Table of contents and notes; McKim, James Miller
      see SLAVERY E 441 M46 v. 65
    - Cleveland Freedmen's Union Commission, September 1866 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Report
    - Clothier, John W., December 6, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Coates, Benjamin, 1867-1868 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Coates, Edwin H., 1860-1861 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Cobb, Nehemiah, 1867-1868 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Hodson, John
    - Coffin, C.G., June 17, 1861 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Coffin, Charles F., 1866-1867 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Coffin, Levi, 1865-1868 (Box 12, Folder 21-25)
      Letter/s to Cadbury, B.H.; McKim, James Miller; Walden, John Morgan; unknown
    - Coffin, Peter, 1832-1834 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      Letter/s to May, Lucretia F.
    - Coit, Rosetta A., 1868-1869 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Coleman, Cecile H., 1869 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Coleman, Nathan, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 29-30)
    - Colfax, Schuyler, 1866-1867 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Collins, Charles, March 7, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      Agnew, Cornelius Rea
    - Collins, Ellen (Box 12, Folder 33)
      Beeman, Eunice M.; Eastman, Lucy
    - Collins, J.W., 1870 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Collins & Brother, 1868-1869 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      Itemized receipts for Bacon, Harriet E.; Collins, Ellen; Cardoza, T. W.; Continuing Committee, New York Branch A.F.U.C.; New York Branch Freedmen's Union commission; Shaw, Francis George; Estes, E.C.
    - Collyer, Robert, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      Bur, Jona
    - Colton, Erastus, 1867-1869 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      Receipt; Telegram to American Freedmens Union Commission; McKim, James Miller
    - Colton, Mary T., 1867 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      Letter/s to Walden, John Morgan; unknown
    - Converse, Henry, January 10, 1868 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Conway, Thomas W., 1866 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Cook, Mrs. C.M., February 20, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Cooke, Jay, April 14, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Cooke, Martha A., September 28, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Cooper, Joseph, 1869-1871 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Cope, Francis R., 1866-1867 (Box 12, Folder 45-46)
    - Cope, M.C., January 18, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Core, John, July 8, 1868 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Corson, Hiram, January 29, 1860 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Corson, Robert Rodgers, 1866-1869 (Box 12, Folder 50-52)
      Baird, George William
    - Cowdery, A.A., March 25, 1844 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Craighead, Rebecca M., 1867-1868 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Crandell, L.A., 1866 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Crandon, T. Frank, June 19, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Crane, Jane Eliza, Undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Brewer, D.R.
    - Crawford, M.D.C., 1866 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Crawford, Samuel, December 10, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      Letter/s to American Freedman's Union Commission
    - Crews, A., 1868 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      Receipts for Bond, S.A.
    - Crews, J.B., December 25, 1868 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      Crews, A.
    - Criswell, R.J., April 23, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      Letter/s to Estes, E.C.
    - Crocker, L., 1867 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Crooks, S.B., 1867 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      Letter/s to Kennedy, Crammond; McKim, James Miller
    - Cummings, Katie, October 14, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      Application for a teahing position; Recommendations from Johnson, T.J. and Weeks, Alonzo; 4 paychecks
    - Cupidon, Charles Theodore (?), 1845 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Membres de la Societe de l'abolition de l'Esclavage
    - Curtis, George William, November 2, 1867- (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Cushing, Joseph M., 1867-1868 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Cushings and Bailey, March 8, 1870; Cushings & Bailey (Box 12, Folder 69)
      Itemized receipt for Harrison, Charles A.
    - Dailey, Julia E., June 27, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      2 Applications for teaching positions; Recommendations from Lattimore, S.A. and Steele, Daniel; Application for teaching position for Ordensa E. Delano
    - Dairy, Ignatius, October 1795 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Letter/s to Manumission
    - Dana, Charles Anderson, November 17, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Darlington, Catherine Lacey (Mrs. William), June 29, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Letter/s to McKim, Sarah Allibone Speakman (Mrs. James Miller)
    - Darvelas Dorval, J.F., March 3, 1847 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Edward M., 1861-1867 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Garrett, Thomas
    - Davis, Henry Winter, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Davis, William Morris, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Day, Howard M., May 12, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Day, William Howard, May 21, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Dean, Jabez, of Norwich, Connecticut, June 29, 1749 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Bill of sale
    - Delano, Ordensa E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Lattimore, S.A. and Steele, Daniel
      Dailey, Julia E.
    - Denison, Charles Wheeler, April 14, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Dennis, Susan, June 22, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Letter concerning her teaching position; Recommendation written by Hewes, J.T.; 2 paychecks; 3 shipping tickets
    - de Watteville, Bernard R., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - de Watteville, Elisa (nee de Portes), April 5, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Letter/s to Shaw, Francis George
    - Dewey, Clara E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Dewey, C.; Fowler, Henry; Merriman, C.H.
    - Dewitt, Andrew J., October 14, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Arthur, A.A.; Buford, R.D.; Goggin, Wm. L.; Haymond, L.S.; Johnson, James F.; and Jordan and Hardy
    - Dexter, Charlotte L., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Barnard, M.R.; Barney, C.W.; Hardy, Jane L.; Wukkuansm S.G.
    - Dexter, Wirt, January 11, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Dibble, O.C., December 2, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Letter/s to Gillespie, John
    - Dickey, Hugh D., January 13, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Dickson, Henry, January 24, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Dike, Henry A., 1866-1867 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Alvord, Henry Elijah
    - Dill, Joseph B.M., January 9, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Dingee, W.W., September 6, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Diossy, R.K., September 15, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Dixon, George, September 9, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Dodge, William Earl, July 29, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Dodson, James B. (heirs), April 1819 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Draft of an appeal to the county court in Richmond
    - Doolittle, Harriet, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Recommendation for a teaching position from Copeland, J.
    - Douglass, Frederick, May 2, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Douglass, Harriet M., Undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Board of Instruction, Fort Henry; Ransom, C.
    - Douglass, Martha A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Dox, H.L., 1865-1866 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Walden, John Morgan
    - Draper, Amos, December 24, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Drury, A.K., May 23, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - DuBois, N., 1864 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Duffield, Divie Bethune, March 3, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Duffield, George, 1838-1866 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      Letter/s to Convention of Delegates from Freedmen's Aid Commissions; McKim, James Miller; unknown
    - Duffield, George, Jr., 1867 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Duffield, Isabella Graham, October 18, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Dugdale, Joseph A., 1858-1861 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      Notice to the Executive Committee of the Pennsylvania Anti-Slavery Society; McKim, James Miller
    - Duke, S.A., September 2, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Duncan, E.B., August 14, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      Letter/s to Executive Committee of the Union Commission
    - Durant, Thomas Jefferson, October 23, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Durkee, J.N., October 21, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      Letter/s to Dennett, N.C.
    - Duryea, Joseph Tuthill, February 19, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Dutton, Kate M., Undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Fletcher, H.; Stoddard, Abishai
    - Dyer, Mary E., August 1, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Shorburn, Alex. McA.
    - Dyson, R.H., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Earle, Edward, January 20, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Earle, George Hussey, 1861-1863 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Easter, John D., September 4, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Eastman, Addson W., August 11, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Bates, S.L.; Blake, S.A.; Howard, Leonard; Little, J.S.; Webster, A.
    - Eastman, Lucy, Undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Gilbert, John I.; Harper, John; Leonard, Lucy A.; Miller, L. Merill; Wead, L.C.; 6 receipts
    - Eastman, M.A., September 17, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Eaton, D.L., July 11, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Eaton, Lizzie, July 14, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Eaton, William Hadley, March 24, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      Letter/s to Ward, George Cabot
    - Eberhart, G.L., January 16, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      Letter/s to Shipherd, Jacob R.
    - Eddy, Thomas M., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Edwards, G.G., March 20, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      Letter/s to Roe, Rev. C.H.
    - Edwards, Samuel, January 8, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Edwards, Thomas, September 16, 1824 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      Letter/s to High Police Officer of Philadelphia
    - Ellicott, M.T., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Elliott, George, January 8, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Elis, George W., January 19, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Ellsworth, Imogene, Undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
      Application for teaching position; Recommendations from Dennett, N.C. and Hart, Edwin J.
    - Elwell, Rebecca, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Bacon, Wm. T. Jr.; Burton, N.J.; Churchill, Jno; Ferris, Mrs. Lockwood; Gunn, F.W.; Mead, Edmund; Mead, William J.; Robinson, Chas. E.; Thompson, F.M.
    - Emerson, Hattie E., July 30, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      Application for teaching position; Recommendation from Kinne, A.E.
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, August 26, 1856 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Estes, E.C., 1866-1869 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      List of expenses; Resolution; Collins, Ellen; Israel, Fielder; McKim, James Miller
    - Estlin, Mary A., 1859-1868 (Box 13, Folder 73.5-74)
      A list of books; McKim, James Miller
      Chesson, F.W.
    - Eustis, F.A., March 1861 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Evans, Charles E., January 31, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      Copy of teacher's license
    - Fairchild, James Harris, February 16, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Fairchild, W.B., March 13, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Fauntleroy, Moore, July 20, 1790 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - Fauntleroy, William, October 26, 1757 (Box 13, Folder 80)
      Will
    - Felton, Rosina E., October 4, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Fields, J.W., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Fisher, E., August 11, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Fisher, Helen C., 1866-1867 (Box 13, Folder 84)
      Wilde, Lizzie H.
    - Fisher, Sydney George, November 19, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 85)